Andrey Fedorovich

Front-end developer - Kyiv, Ukraine

+375 29 828 99 07 a.fedorovich@protonmail.com

About

Web developer with over 3 years of experience

Participated in the development of browser extensions, desktop applications, websites, e-mails and PDF documents

Strong knowledge about UI development (accessibility, semantic, optimization)

Understanding OOP, Design Pattern

Experience with build systems (e.g Webpack, Gulp)

I enjoy learning and helping others to learn new things

Preferred stack







React







JavaScript

Next.js

CSS Modules

Git

Figma

Work experience

Javascript Developer at PixelPlex Belarus, Minsk Feb 2018 - Present

UI developer at DShop24 Belarus, Minsk Feb 2016 - Nov 2016

Education

Belarusian State University
Bachelor`s degree, faculty of social and cultural communications
Cultural studies (2011 - 2016)